

EDUCATION

BSC. COMPUTER SCIENCE

Anchor University 2020-2023

OND GEOLOGY

University of Lagos 2018-2019

BSC. ANATOMY

University of Benin 2013-2017

REFERENCE

Tunde Thani

Director I Explicit Comms. T:+234-70-6381-6900

Dalia Lopez Mills

AD I Parachute Media Group

T:+1-613-555-0174

Phone

+234 81 2017 9204 +234 90 3852 0113

Email

ojeriakhijeza@gmail.com jezaojeriakhi@gmail.com

Address

31, Oklar Royale Ave, Gemade Estate. Lagos, Nigeria.

Zip Code - 100234

Portfolio

jezastudio.github.io/creative-portfolio

JEZA OJERIAKHI

CREATIVE DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm Jeza. I'm a Creative Designer with over 8 years of experience in my field working with businesses and individuals to achieve their goals. I am profecient at using AI, Ae, Ps, Figma, XD and CorelDraw as well as HTML/CSS/JavaScript & Wordpress. My Skills include:

- Graphic Design, Illustrations & Motion Graphics.
- Branding & Social Media Management.
- UI/UX Design & Product Design.
- Front-End Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017-2018 GRAPHIC DESIGNER
Oaks Communication Ltd/ Lagos Nigeria
- Developing unique brand identities, logos, and comprehensive brand guidelines.

2018-2020 CREATIVE DESIGNER

Parachute Design Group/Toronto Canada

- From graphic designs to motion graphics, creating brand identities to social media management and much more

2020-2023 ART DIRECTOR

Explicit Communication/Lagos Nigeria

- Working with a team of talented creatives in handling content creation, coming up with intuitive brand marketing strategies, copywriting, graphic designs, product design, web design, and much more.

CERTIFICATIONS

COURSERA CERTIFICATES

- UI/UX Specialization
 - UX Design Fundamentals
 - Web Design: Strategy & Information Architecture
 - Web Design: Wireframes to Prototypes
- Front-End Development

SOFTWARE SKILL

Adobe photoshop	Microsoft Office Tools
Adobe Illustrator	CorelDraw
Figma	HTML-S/CSS-3
Adobe Animate	WordPress